Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
Suporte administrativo. Assista em kissasia.cam ou kisskh.org.
Take a good look.
Observe com atenção.
This is what you wanted.
Era isso que queria.
Today,
Hoje,
you just need to feel my warmth.
Só precisa de sentir o meu calor.
Kneel.
Ajoelhe-se.
Take your clothes off.
Tire as suas roupas.
Why are you burning hot?
Porque está com tanto calor?
Because I took a shower.
Porque tomei um banho.
A shower?
Um banho?
Didn't you take a cold shower?
Não tomou um banho frio?
It happens.
Acontece.
Come to me.
Venha até mim.
I asked you to come.
Eu convidei-te para vir.
How are you
Como estás
going to spend the 2,000 dollars
Vou gastar os 2.000 dólares.
apart from your mother's surgery?
Para além da cirurgia da sua mãe?
I want to go to Florence.
Quero ir a Florença.
I want to see the real French Renaissance.
Quero ver o verdadeiro Renascimento francês.
Florence?
Florença?
With 2,000 dollars?
Com 2.000 dólares?
Yeah.
Sim.
To see the real Renaissance.
Para presenciar o verdadeiro Renascimento.
We only signed a sleeping contract.
Assinámos apenas um contrato para dormir.
Now,
Agora,
can you sign a contract with me?
Pode assinar um contrato comigo?
What do you mean?
O que queres dizer?
Like this.
Assim.
Are you game for a blood contract?
Topa um pacto de sangue?
Even if you're hungry, eating without permission
Mesmo que esteja com fome, coma sem permissão.
is a bad habit.
É um mau hábito.
If you want to eat,
Se quiser comer,
tell me with your mouth.
Diga-me com a sua boca.
Like this.
Assim.
Good boy.
Bom menino.
Slow down or you might get hurt.
Vá mais devagar ou pode magoar-se.
From now on, only eat what I give you.
De hoje em diante, coma apenas o que eu lhe der.
Mr. Han.
Senhor Ele.
Are you really a rich heir?
É mesmo um herdeiro rico?
Aren't you cold-blooded?
Não é insensível?
I guess you eat kimchi stew too.
Imagino que também coma ensopado de kimchi.
What about you?
E tu?
Don't art students live on inspiration?
Será que os estudantes de arte não vivem de inspiração?
Look at you, gobbling that bread.
Olha só para ti, a devorar este pão.
Eat that.
Coma isso.
It's way better.
É muito melhor.
You know...
Sabes...
I heard rumors
Ouvi rumores
that you played Chopin all night
que tocou Chopin a noite toda
in front of the College of Music for a girl.
em frente à Faculdade de Música para uma menina.
You're really imaginative.
É muito criativo(a).
Use that imagination in your art instead.
Use essa imaginação na sua arte.
Also,
Também,
I didn't do it for a girl.
Eu não o fiz por causa de uma rapariga.
It was just a punishment for a game.
Foi apenas um castigo por causa de um jogo.
If you say such nonsense again,
Se disser esse disparate de novo,
I'll only feed you iced Americano.
Só te vou servir café americano gelado.
Why iced Americano?
Porquê um Americano gelado?
Aren't you going to answer me?
Não me vai responder?
I don't like iced Americano.
Eu não gosto de café americano gelado.
Eat your food.
Coma a sua comida.